Daro Yamamoto

Senior Blockchain Developer & Full Stack Developer

(+81).895222743 daro1202@outlook.com github.com/daro1202 Uwajima, Ehime Prefecture, Japan

SUMMARY

I'm Daro Yamamoto, with 7 years of development experiences as the Full Stack Developer, Project Manager and Blockhain developer. I'm always learning. Win2Win is my main working style, and it shows how I work with clients. I love to help Blockchain Startup companies as a project manager, developer.

Work Experience.

FULLSTACK DEVELOPER INTERN 2017- 2021

- Developed various websites using React, Vue, Next.
- · Developed Backend using Laravel, Nodejs, Express with Database such as mysql, mongoDB, SQLite.

Blockchain DEVELOPER 2020- 2021

- · Designed and developed NFTsRealm Marketplace website from scratch using Solidity.
- · Developed smart contracts for NFT marketplace.

Projects.

Tenyoshi MERN Stack

Tempura and tea soba shop in Uwajima Kisaiya Road

Github

- It is a tempura, and tea soba shop in Uwajima Kisaiya Road.
- They are also open for lunch at a reasonable price.
- Developed a single page application using MERN Stack.
- · Used Redux for the data management in Front-End and also used JWT authentication for user authentication in Back-End.
- tenyoshi.com

Growal React.js

Accelerate the growth of the world

Github

- $\bullet\,$ Updated the HTML landing page into React.js.
- Used React-Router to turn the application into Single Page Application.
- $\bullet \ growal.com$

JSCM MERN Stack

Japan Society for Class Management | Classroom

Github

- This recognizes diversity and considers evidence-based and versatile class management practices and theories, aiming to go back and forth between theory and practice regarding class management.
- · Developed using MERN Stack for the efficiency.
- Used the functional components in almost pages, react-redux and saga in Front-End
- Used JWT authentication for the system secure and user management.
- · classroom.gift

Good Feet Store MERN Stack

Personally Fit Arch Support Inserts | The Good Feet Store

Github

- Good Feet Arch Supports are designed to alleviate foot, knee, hip, and back pain. This site shows how they work for you with a free
 personalized arch support fitting and test walk at The Good Feet Store.
- Developed using PHP framework, Laravel.
- · goodfeet.com

Ring Counter CNN, PyTorch,

IMAGE CLASSIFICATION FOR RECOGNITION OF METAL RING's REGION Github • Used metal ring's images to train a model applying multiple types of CNN architecture and Transfer Learning and attained an accuracy of 98.2%.

Technical Skills_

Strongest Areas Data Structures, Algorithms, DB, Web Development,

Blockchain technology

Programming Languages C/C++, Javascript/typescript, PHP, Python, Node **Libraries/Frameworks** React.js, Express.js, Next.js, Vue.js, Git, Jquery, CSS3,

PyTorch, Laravel, CI, etc

Database MongoDB, MySQL, SQLite

Platforms Vercel, Heroku

Education_

Bachelor of computer science Shikoku University - Graduated

• 7.94/10

June. 2009 - May.
2014

Shikoku, Japan

Publications.

An overlapping sliding window and combined features based emotion recognition system for EEG signals Yasuke Suzuki, Hiro Genzi,

Applied Computing and Informatics(2014).DOi:10.1108/ACI-03-2014-0126

Achievements and Recognition

2021 Blockchain technology, Hightest Rating 1640 and solved 500+ coding problems

2017 Web Master

2015-2016 **Top 10 teams among 50 teams**, Code Break 1.0 hackathon conducted by MIT WPU.

OCTOBER 17, 2021 Daro · RÉSUMÉ